icajobguarantee.com 2017-12-18

# PrivacyPolicy- ICA Job Guarantee

ICA Infotech Pvt Ltd, (“ICA”) is committed to protecting any personal information you provide in connection with your use of this website, (the "Site"). This Privacy Policy describes what information we collect when you visit the Site, how we collect it, how we use it and the steps we take to protect it. The privacy policy may be updated from time to time without notice and you are requested to review the policy periodically. By submitting information to us or continuing to use the Site after we have posted any modifications, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, which are incorporated into and a part of our Terms.

**Subscribing to Training Courses and Purchasing E-Learning Materials**

If you wish to subscribe totraining courses or purchase E-Learning Materials, you will automatically be redirected to the ICA registration page. ICA will collect and use your personal information in accordance with the privacy policy posted in the Site. We encourage all visitors who wish to subscribe totraining courses or purchase E-Learning Materials from ICA to read our privacy policy so that you will know how your personal information will be collected, used, and shared.

**Information Gathered Through The Site**

ICA may track and record certain non-personal information of Site users, including IP address, operating system, type of browser, referring URL, and time spent on the Site in order to gain aggregate data that may be analyzed for trends and statistics on how our visitors use the Site. ICA may use accumulated aggregate non-personal data for several purposes including, but not limited to, Site traffic analysis, evaluation of ICA's services, and program planning. ICA may also market anonymous, non-identifiable user data that has been collected and processed into aggregate and anonymous statistical profiles to third parties. ICA may use a third-party website analytics provider to track and record non-personal information of Site users and provide reports based on such information to ICA. Such providers may use that non-personal information for their internal purposes.

ICA will only collect personal information of users (i.e. name, postal address, email address, credit card number, telephone number), if those users wish to contact us, register for courses, or receive notification of new products or upcoming courses. ICA will only use your personal information for the purposes for which you provide it. If, after registering for any such notifications, you no longer wish to be contacted regarding ICA services or activities that we think may be of interest to you, you may let us know at any time by sending an email to crm@icagroup.inor contacting us as described below.  We may also share your personal information with third parties who provide services to us in connection with the Site or disclose it in special circumstances if we have a good-faith belief that it is necessary to enforce this Privacy Policy, protect the safety of any one or that such disclosure is required by law.

**Links**

The Site may contain links to other websites that are owned or controlled by third parties. Please note that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from those of the Site. ICA is not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of any linked website. We encourage you to read the privacy policy of any website you wish to visit before disclosing any information.

**Other Notification**

In order to implement or enforce this Privacy Policy or other Terms or to notify users ICA may use information you have provided to contact you.

**Enforcement**

If ICA becomes aware that the security of the Site is compromised or any non-public user information has been disclosed to unrelated third parties as a result of external activity or otherwise not in accordance with this Privacy Policy, ICA will take reasonable measures that it deems appropriate (which may include an internal investigation and reporting, notifying the user, and notifying and cooperating with law enforcement authorities)

**Security**

We will use reasonable efforts to safeguard any personal information that you provide through the Site. Nevertheless, we do not guarantee any transmission over the Internet to be 100% secure.

**Service Providers**

Our service providers may not be located in your geographic area. By providing your personal information on the Site, you also consent to the transfer of your data to these service providers.

**Contact Us**

If you have questions or concerns about these Terms or the Site or if you wish to update, correct or delete any information you have provided to us, please contact ICA at crm@icagroup.in or through the information below:

**ICA Infotech Pvt Ltd**

27 Netaji Subhas Road, 4th Floor

Kolkata 700001
